ecigs.net.au 2014-02-14

# Electronic Cigarettes Australia Pty Ltd - Aussie Blue® Ecigs - Southern Cross E-Liquids - Privacy Policy

We understand that your privacy while using our Site is important, especially when conducting business or providing sensitive personal information. This Notice will govern our Privacy Policy for users of this Site, whether or not a transaction of any sort is conducted while visiting.

 **Your Personal Information** : The information we learn from customers helps us to personalize and continually improve our customer service, while developing ways to improve your shopping experience with us. Following is some of the information we gather about our users.

 **Information You Provide Us** : When you provide us with your information such as: name, address, phone, fax, e-mail address and business information (if applicable). We use this information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, communicating with you and customizing future shopping for you.

 **Are Cookies Used On Our Site** : We use cookies to obtain a variety of information which provides us details as to what product and information interest our visitors view the most. Cookies can also be used to protect your information. If you wish to disable our cookie from obtaining this information, you can seek programs that will allow you to visit our site anonymously.

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. We can see what pages you click through, plus store items in your Shopping Cart between visits. The 'Help' portion of the toolbar on most browsers will instruct you on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, and/or how to disable cookies altogether.

 **Do we Share the Information we Receive?** : Absolutely not. Under no circumstances will we ever give away or sell your personal information to anyone else for any reason whatsoever, without prior written approval from yourself. Any information we gain through our use of customer polls, surveys, cookies, session tracking or anything else, is used internally and for the sole purpose of providing you better service. If you are on our mailing list and you ask us to remove you, we will immediately. As we do with our own, we respect your privacy.

 **How Secure Is Information About Me?** : Your personal information is only accessible to a limited number of qualified people who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. Sensitive information is protected by encryption protocols, in place to protect information sent over the Internet.

While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electronic communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable for any such occurrences. You will find that almost all Internet e-commerce providers make this same claim, especially if they use privacy policy templates such as this one to make known their company or organisation privacy policies.

 **What Choices Do I Have?** : As discussed above, you always have the choice not to provide information, even though it might be needed to make a purchase with us. You can add or update certain information using the MyAccount page at any time. If you do not want to receive e-mails or other mail from us, simply remove yourself from the mailing list via the MyAccount page.

 **Are Children Allowed to Use our Site?** : No! Our products are only sold to adult smokers, of legal smoking age for their region.

 **Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions** : If you choose to visit our Site, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice and our Conditions of Use.If you have any concern about privacy on our site, please contact us with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.

Because our business changes constantly, our Privacy Notice and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web Site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
